let questionEasy = [
  {
    question: "Add two numbers, 5 and 3.",
    options: {
      optionA: "result = 5 + 3",
      optionB: "result = 5 * 3",
      optionC: "result = 5 - 3",
    },
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "Print the phrase Hello, World! in Python",
    options: {
      optionA: "print(Hi, Earth!)",
      optionB: "print(Greetings!)",
      optionC: "print(Hello, World!)",
    },
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    question: "Check if the number 7 is equal to 7",
    options: {
      optionA: "is_equal = (7 == 7)",
      optionB: "is_equal = (7 != 7)",
      optionC: "is_equal = (7 > 7)",
    },
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "Create a list with three elements: apple, banana, cherry",

    options: {
      optionA: "fruits = {apple, banana, cherry}",
      optionB: "fruits = (apple, banana, cherry)",
      optionC: "fruits = [apple, banana, cherry]",
    },
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    question: "Multiply the number 4 by 6",
    options: {
      optionA: "result = 4 * 6",
      optionB: "result = 4 + 6",
      optionC: "result = 4 / 6",
    },
    answer: "optionA",
  },
];

let questionMedium = [
  {
    question: "In JavaScript, what does the this keyword refer to?",
    options: {
      optionA: "The global object",
      optionB: "The object on which the current function is invoked",
      optionC: "The current function's prototype",
    },
    answer: "optionB",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following sorting algorithms has the best average-case time complexity?",
    options: {
      optionA: "Bubble Sort",
      optionB: "Quick Sort",
      optionC: "Insertion Sort",
    },
    answer: "optionB",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does the acronym REST stand for in the context of web development?",

    options: {
      optionA: "Representational State Transfer",
      optionB: "Remote Execution of Server Tasks",
      optionC: "Really Simple Transfer",
    },
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In Python, what is the purpose of the self keyword in a class method?",
    options: {
      optionA: "It is a reserved keyword with no specific purpose",
      optionB: "It is used to create a new instance of the class",
      optionC: "It refers to the instance of the class itself",
    },
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In JavaScript, what is the purpose of the addEventListener method?",
    options: {
      optionA: "To attach an event handler function to an element",
      optionB: "To remove an element from the DOM",
      optionC: "To change the style of an element",
    },
    answer: "optionA",
  },
];

let questionHard = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the CSS specificity hierarchy used to determine the precedence of s",
    options: {
      optionA:
        "Class specificity > Inline styles > ID specificity > Element specificity",
      optionB:
        "Element specificity > Class specificity > ID specificity > Inline styles",
      optionC:
        "ID specificity > Class specificity > Element specificity > Inline styles",
    },
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which HTML5 attribute is used to associate a <label> with a form control?",
    options: {
      optionA: "connect",
      optionB: "for",
      optionC: "link",
    },
    answer: "optionB",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the difference between let and const in JavaScript variable declarations?",

    options: {
      optionA: "let allows reassignment, while const does not",
      optionB: "let is block-scoped, while const is function-scoped",
      optionC:
        "let is used for primitive types, while const is used for objects",
    },
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a closure in JavaScript?",

    options: {
      optionA: "A function declared inside another function",
      optionB: "A method for closing and terminating functions",
      optionC: "The process of closing the browser after running a script",
    },
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the CSS property z-index",
    options: {
      optionA: "It defines the rotation axis for transformed elements.",
      optionB: "It sets the order of stacked elements along the z-axis.",
      optionC: "It controls the opacity of an element",
    },
    answer: "optionB",
  },
];
